

//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers -html questions
let questionshtml =[
    {
        numb:"1)",
        question:"HTML stands for",
        answer:"HyperText Markup Language",
        options :[
            "HighText Machine Language",
            "HyperText and links Markup Language",
            "HyperText Markup Language",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"2)",
        question:"  The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is r",
        answer:"HTML, Head, Title, Body",
        options :[
            "Head, Title, HTML, body",
            "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
            "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
            "HTML, Head, Title, Body"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"3)",
        question:"  Which of the following attribute is used to provide a unique name to an element?",
        answer:"id",
        options :[
            "class",
            "id",
            "type",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"4)",
        question:"  What are the types of unordered or bulleted list in HTML?",
        answer:"disc, circle, square",
        options :[
            "disc, square, triangle",
            "polygon, triangle, circle",
            "disc, circle, square",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"5)",
        question:"  Which of the following HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?",
        answer:"style",
        options :[
            "style",
            "type",
            "class",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },

]

//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers -JS questions
let questionsjs =[
    {
        numb:"1)",
        question:"Which type of JavaScript language is ___",
        answer:"Object-Based",
        options :[
            "Object-Oriented",
            "Object-Based",
            "Assembly-language",
            "High-level"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"2)",
        question:"  Which of the following is the correct output for the following JavaScript code:",
        answer:"1",
        options :[
            "1",
            "Error",
            "10",
            "5"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"3)",
        question:"  Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
        answer:"immediate if",
        options :[
            "Alternative to if-else",
            "Switch statement",
            "If-then-else statement",
            "immediate if"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"4)",
        question:"  In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?",
        answer:"block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
        options :[
            "Conditional block",
            "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
            "both conditional block and a single statement",
            "block that contains a single statement"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"5)",
        question:" When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:",
        answer:"Ignores the statements",
        options :[
            "Shows a warning",
            "Prompts to complete the statement",
            "Throws an error",
            "Ignores the statements"
        ]
    },

]

//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers -css questions
let questionscss =[
    {
        numb:"1)",
        question:"CSS stands for -",
        answer:"Cascading style sheets",
        options :[
            "Cascade style sheets",
            "Color and style sheets",
            "Cascading style sheets",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"2)",
        question:" The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is -",
        answer:"background-color",
        options :[
            "bgcolor",
            "color",
            "background-color",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"3)",
        question:" The CSS property used to control the element's font-size is  ",
        answer:"font-size",
        options :[
            "text-style",
            "text-size",
            "font-size",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"4)",
        question:" Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property for the padding properties?",
        answer:"padding",
        options :[
            "padding-left",
            "padding-right",
            "padding",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"5)",
        question:" Which of the following CSS property is used to set the background image of an element?",
        answer:"background-image",
        options :[
            "background-attachment",
            "background-image",
            "background-color",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },

]

//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers -react js questions
let questionsreactjs =[
    {
        numb:"1)",
        question:"Which of the following is the correct name of React.js?",
        answer:"All of the above",
        options :[
            "React",
            "React.js",
            "ReactJS",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"2)",
        question:" Which of the following are the advantages of React.js?",
        answer:"All of the above",
        options :[
            "React.js can increase the application's performance with Virtual DOM.",
            "React.js is easy to integrate with other frameworks such as Angular, BackboneJS since it is only a view library.",
            "React.js can render both on client and server side.",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"3)",
        question:"Which of the following is not a disadvantage of React.js? ",
        answer:"The JSX in React.js makes code easy to read and write.",
        options :[
            "React.js has only a view layer. We have put your code for Ajax requests, events and so on.",
            "The library of React.js is pretty large",
            "The JSX in React.js makes code easy to read and write.",
            "The learning curve can be steep in React.js."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"4)",
        question:" Which of the following command is used to install create-react-app?",
        answer:"npm install -g create-react-app",
        options :[
            "npm install -g create-react-app",
            "npm install create-react-app",
            "npm install -f create-react-app",
            "install -g create-react-app"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"5)",
        question:" What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        answer:"Virtual DOM",
        options :[
            "Original DOM",
            "Virtual DOM",
            "Both A and B.",
            "None of the above."
        ]
    },

]

//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers -Angular js questions
let questionsAngularjs =[
    {
        numb:"1)",
        question:"Which of the following statement is correct for AngularJS?",
        answer:"AngularJS is a JavaScript framework",
        options :[
            "AngularJS is an HTML framework",
            "AngularJS is a Java framework",
            "AngularJS is a JavaScript framework",
            "AngularJS is a SQL framework"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"2)",
        question:"  On which of the Architectural pattern AngularJS is based?",
        answer:"MVVM Architectural pattern",
        options :[
            "Observer Pattern",
            "Decorator pattern",
            "MVC Architecture pattern",
            "MVVM Architectural pattern"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"3)",
        question:"AngularJS is perfect for? ",
        answer:"SPAs",
        options :[
            "SPAs",
            "MPAs",
            "DPAs",
            "CPAs"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"4)",
        question:" Which of the following command is used to install create-react-app?",
        answer:"npm install -g create-react-app",
        options :[
            "npm install -g create-react-app",
            "npm install create-react-app",
            "npm install -f create-react-app",
            "install -g create-react-app"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"5)",
        question:" Which of the following directive is used to bind the application data to the HTML view in AngularJS?",
        answer:"ng-bind directive",
        options :[
            "ng-app directive",
            "ng-model directive",
            "ng-bind directive",
            "ng-init directive"
        ]
    },

]

//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers -Typescript questions
let questionsTs =[
    {
        numb:"1)",
        question:"Which are the different Data Types supported by Typescript?",
        answer:" All of the above mentioned",
        options :[
            "Boolean var bValue: boolean = false",
            "Number var age: number = 16",
            "String var name: string = 'jon'",
            " All of the above mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"2)",
        question:"  Which statements are true regarding JSX modes?",
        answer:"The preserve mode will keep the JSX as part of the output to be further consumed by another transform step",
        options :[
            "These modes only affect the emit stage - type checking is unaffected",
            "The output of react mode will have a .jsx file extension",
            "The react mode will emit React.addElement",
            "The preserve mode will keep the JSX as part of the output to be further consumed by another transform step"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"3)",
        question:"What are variables in Typescript? ",
        answer:"All",
        options :[
            "A variable name should contain alphabets and numeric digits",
            "It cannot contain spaces and special characters except underscore (_) and dollar ($) sign",
            "A variable name cannot begin with a digit",
            "All"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"4)",
        question:" What are the variable scopes available in TypeScript?",
        answer:"All of the above",
        options :[
            "Global Scope",
            "Class Scope",
            "Local Scope",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"5)",
        question:" What are the benefits of Typescript?",
        answer:"All of the above",
        options :[
            "It helps in code structuring",
            "Use class based object oriented programming",
            "Impose coding guidelines",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },

]

//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers -.Net questions
let questionsdotnet =[
    {
        numb:"1)",
        question:"Which webserver is developed by Microsoft?",
        answer:"Internet Information Services (IIS)",
        options :[
            "Apache Tomcat",
            "Caudium",
            "Internet Information Services (IIS)",
            "WEBrick"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"2)",
        question:"Which protocol is used to transfer files frtom localhost to remote host?",
        answer:"FTP",
        options :[
            "HTTP",
            "FTP",
            "TCP",
            "UDP"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"3)",
        question:"Which commands are used to specify settings of an .aspx file? ",
        answer:"Directives",
        options :[
            "Class",
            "Directives",
            "Events",
            "Validation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"4)",
        question:" Which of the following directive is used to link an assembly to a page or user control?",
        answer:"@Assembly",
        options :[
            "@Page",
            "@Import",
            "@Assembly",
            "@Reference"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:"5)",
        question:"The @Implements directive",
        answer:"indicates that a page or user control implements a specified .NET Framework interface",
        options :[
            "imports a namespace into current page page or user control",
            "assigns a class or virtual path used to type the Master property of a page",
            "indicates that a page or user control implements a specified .NET Framework interface",
            "none of these above"
        ]
    },

]

